http://vision-supplies.com/privacypolicy

Select Store:
UK
EU
International
Select Currency:
Wishlist
(0)
Shopping cart
(0)
You have no items in your shopping cart
T: +44 (0) 1926 611745  |  E: sales@vision-supplies.com  |  Skype Online Now  |
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Intervision Global Ltd (trading as Vision-supplies.com) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the Vision-supplies.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Intervision Global Ltd.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may, either through third parties or directly, collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider utilised and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance user experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
To find out more please read our Cookie Policy.
How we use collected information
Vision-supplies.com may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
Accept and fulfil customer orders
Administer and enhance the website
To improve customer service
To personalise user experience
To send emails in relation to a sale
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
We may use the email address to respond to their enquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If the User decides to opt-out of our mailing lists, they will not receive relevant emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, special offers etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the foot of each email.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We will only disclose personal information to third parties for the purpose of goods delivery.  We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes only.
Internet Advertising
We will occasionally use online advertising networks to advertise our website services.  We do not provide any personal information to advertisers or third party sites that display our adverts. However, advertisers and other third-parties (including ad networks, ad-serving companies, and other service providers they may use) may assume that users who interact with or click on an advert or content are part of the group that the ad or content is directed towards. Also, some third-parties may provide us information about you (such as demographic information or sites where you have been shown ads) from offline and online sources that we may use to provide you more relevant and useful advertising.
Changes to this privacy policy
Vision Supplies reserves the right to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
Vision-supplies.com, Unit 1, Bunkers Hill, Welsh Road, Leamington Spa, CV33 9BE, United Kingdom
Wait...
Copyright © 2020 Vision-Supplies . All rights reserved.
Powered by nopCommerce
